That was probably
our second-best
potato chip war ever.
What the hell ?!
We'll clean it
up later, dude.
I'm not your "dude," and
you never clean anything up.
Well, we mean to, but then we leave, and then
we come back, and it's already cleaned up.
You eat my food,
you dirty up my house
and every time I
go into a bedroom,
I have to wonder about finding one
of you naked with some poor girl !
Well, at least you know that if you
find me naked in a room, I'm by myself.
All right, I want everybody who doesn't
live in this house to get out now !
You know what ? You're
a real bummer, man.
Come on, fez, let's
go to our new apartment
where people can do whatever
they want, whenever they want.
Just like the bible says,
"let my people do
whatever they want."
eric,
the high school sent over your transcript, which
means you can start applying to teachers' college.
Now you tell me what school you wanna
go to, and I will send them a pie.
Because you cannot eat a lady's pie and
then not let her son into the school.